What's your body count?
Bone Lake is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Mercedes Bryce Morgan.
A couple’s romantic vacation at a secluded lakeside estate is upended when they are
forced to share the mansion with a mysterious and attractive couple.
In this darkly hilarious and seductive horror story, a dream getaway spirals into a nightmarish maze of sex, lies,
and manipulation, bringing terrifying secrets to light and triggering a bloody battle for survival.
Will, played by Alex Roe.
Sage, played by Maddie Hasson.
Diego, played by Marco Pigossi.
Cin, played by Andra Nechita.
Brett, played by Clayton Spencer.
Angie, played by Eliane Reis.
Bone Lake is a 2024 American erotic thriller film directed by Mercedes Bryce Morgan, written by Joshua
Friedlander, and starring Maddie Hasson, Alex Roe, Andra Nechita, and Marco Pigossi.
Its plot follows a couple whose getaway at a remote lakeside house is interrupted by another
mysterious couple, leading to a disturbing series of mind games and manipulation.
The film had its world premiere at Fantastic Fest on September 21, 2024,
and was released in the United States on October 3, 2025.
The film explores themes of marriage proposal,
cheating, sword, hidden camera, murder.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.